A Finding Aid to the Arnold Rönnebeck and Louise Emerson Rönnebeck Papers, 1884-2002, in the Archives of American Art AAA.ronnarno
Archives of American Art
Arnold Rönnebeck and Louise Emerson Rönnebeck papers
1884-2002
AAA.ronnarno
Archives of American Art
4.1 Linear feet
The papers of sculptor Arnold Rönnebeck and painter Louise Emerson Rönnebeck measure 4.1 linear feet and date from 1884-2002. The collection contains biographical material, family and professional correspondence, sketches and drawings, writings, a scrapbook, and printed material. There are also numerous photographic prints, copy prints, negatives, and 7 glass plate negatives of the Rönnebecks and their artwork, travels, family, and friends, including Charles Demuth, Marsden Hartley, Alfred Stieglitz, and Tony Luhan.
Arnold H. Rönnebeck
Provenance
The papers were donated in 2001 by Ursula Moore Works and Arnold Rönnebeck, the artists' daughter and son.
Related Material
Correspondence between Arnold Rönnebeck and Alfred Stieglitz and Marsden Hartley is located at the Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library at Yale University.
Existence and Location of Copies note
The bulk of the collection was digitized in 2015 and is available on the Archives of American Art's website. Due to fragility, original glass plate negatives are closed to researchers. Materials which have not been scanned include blank pages, blank versos of photographs, duplicates, and negatives. In some cases, exhibition catalogs and other publications have had their covers, title pages, and relevant pages scanned.
Restrictions on Access
Use of original papers requires an appointment. Glass plate negatives are housed separately and closed to researchers.
Biographical Note
Sculptor Arnold Rönnebeck (1885-1947) was part of the "Stieglitz circle" and settled in Denver where he served as director of the Denver Art Museum from 1926-1931. Rönnebeck married Louise Emerson (1901-1980) in 1926. Emerson was a painter and muralist who worked on New Deal mural commissions in Colorado and Wyoming.
Arnold Rönnebeck was born in Nassau, Germany and was a noted sculptor and lithographer. From 1905 to 1907, Rönnebeck studied architecture at the Royal Art School in Berlin and spent a year studying sculpture in Munich. In 1908, he moved to Paris where he furthered his studies in sculpture under Aristede Maillol and Emile Bourdelle. From 1914 to 1918, Rönnebeck served as an officer in the German Imperial Army during World War I. In 1923, he emigrated to the United States where he became part of the Stieglitz circle.
In 1925, Rönnebeck visited Mabel Dodge Luhan at her ranch in Taos, New Mexico, where he met his future wife, the painter Louise Emerson, born Mary Louise Harrington Emerson in 1901. After their marriage, the Rönnebecks lived in Denver where Arnold Rönnebeck worked as director of the Denver Art Museum and continued to execute commissioned works, including bas reliefs, portrait busts, and sculptures. He died in Denver, Colorado in 1947. Throughout the 1950s and 1960s, Louise Emerson Rönnebeck continued to receive commissions for frescoes and murals in Colorado and Bermuda and died in Denver, Colorado in 1980.
Scope and Content Note
The papers of sculptor Arnold Rönnebeck and painter Louise Emerson Rönnebeck measure 4.1 linear feet and date from 1884-2002. The collection contains biographical material, family and professional correspondence, sketches and drawings, writings, a scrapbook, and printed material. There are also numerous photographic prints, copy prints, negatives, and 7 glass plate negatives of the Rönnebecks and their artwork, travels, family, and friends, including Charles Demuth, Marsden Hartley, Alfred Stieglitz, and Tony Luhan.
Biographical materials include articles on the Rönnebecks by Betsy Fahlman, curriculum vitae, and documentation on the Emerson family. Correspondence is primarily between Arnold Rönnebeck to Louise, and also includes letters in German to Arnold's sister Irmgard Rönnebeck. Among the professional and personal correspondence from friends and family to both of the Rönnebecks are letters from Kenneth Hayes Miller to Louise Rönnebeck.
Writings include essay drafts, notes, and poetry by the Rönnebecks, including Arnold Rönnebeck's "Paint-As-You-Go Plan." There is a scrapbook of clippings covering Louise Rönnebeck's work. Additional printed material includes Christmas cards, clippings, and exhibition announcements and catalogs of both the Rönnebecks' work. Artwork consists of drawings and sketches by Arnold Rönnebeck.
Photographic materials include photographs of the Rönnebecks and their travels to Arizona, Colorado, New Mexico, New York, and Europe. The series also contains photos, copy prints, negatives, and 7 glass plate negatives of artist friends, and formal and informal documentation of their works of art and public and private art commissions.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as 7 series. Glass plate negatives are housed separately and closed to researchers, but listed where they fall intellectually within the collection.
Series 1: Biographical Materials, 1926-2002 (9 folders; Box 1, OV 7)
Series 2: Correspondence, 1909-1998 (0.6 linear feet; Box 1, 5)
Series 3: Writings, 1920-1944 (6 folders; Box 1, 5)
Series 4: Scrapbook, 1926-1966 (1 folder; Box 1)
Series 5: Printed Material, 1923-1999 (0.5 linear feet; Box 1-2)
Series 6: Artwork, 1915-1950 (2 folders; Box 2, 5)
Series 7: Photographic Materials, 1884-1976 (2.6 linear feet; Box 2-6)
Demuth, Charles, 1883-1935; Hartley, Marsden, 1877-1943; Luhan, Mabel Dodge, 1879-1962; Luhan, Tony; Miller, Kenneth Hayes, 1876-1952; Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, 1901-1980; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946; Artists--New Mexico--Taos; Drawings; Muralists; Photographs; Portrait sculpture; Scrapbooks; Sculptors; Sketches; Women artists
- Biographical Materials, 1926-2002; Series 1; 9 Folders Box 1, OV 7
  Scope and Contents note
  Biographical materials include articles on the Rönnebecks by Betsy Fahlman, curriculum vitae, and documentation on the Emerson family, including genealogical information and artwork by Edith Emerson.
  Existence and Location of Copies note
  This series has been scanned in its entirety.
  Arrangement note
  Materials are minimally arranged by subject and document type.
  - Articles on the Rönnebecks, by Betsy Fahlman, 1996-2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Rönnebeck, Arnold, Curriculum Vitae, circa 1950-1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Rönnebeck, Arnold, Interview Transcript of Art Week Radio, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, Certificates and Passport, 1926, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, Curriculum Vitae, circa 1950-1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Rönnebeck, Irmgard (A. Rönnebeck's sister), Contents of Wallet, 1951-1954 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Emerson Cemetery Plot (Pennsylvania), 1946-1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Oversized materials housed in OV 7.
  - Emerson Family, 1932-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Emerson, Edith, Artwork, circa 1937-1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Oversized Emerson Cemetery Rubbing scanned with Box 1, Folder 7, circa 1941-1967 (Box OV 7)
- Correspondence, 1909-1998; Series 2; 0.6 Linear feet Box 1, 5
  Correspondence is primarily between Arnold Rönnebeck to Louise dating from their courtship and from periods when the Rönnebecks were working on out-of-state art commissions. These include illustrated letters and cover topics ranging from updates on family and friends to the progress of current art projects. There are also letters in German to Arnold's sister Irmgard Rönnebeck, letters of condolence to Louise after Arnold's death, and letters from Louise's extended family and children. Among the professional and personal correspondence to both of the Rönnebecks are letters from Kenneth Hayes Miller to Louise Rönnebeck.
  Correspondence is arranged alphabetically by recipient.
  - Rönnebeck, Arnold, 1909-1947 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Rönnebeck, Arnold to Louise Emerson Rönnebeck, 1925-1936 (Box 1, Folder 11-13)
    Oversized material housed in Box 5, Folder 1.
  - Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, Condolences, A. Rönnebeck's Death, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, Family, 1926-1950 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, Murals, 1940-1951 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, Murals (Bermuda) and Sir John Cox, 1951-1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, Miller, Kenneth Hayes, 1933-1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, Profeit, [Tanti], 1942-1946 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, True, Allen Tupper, 1936-1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, University of Denver, 1946, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, Yale, 1952-1971 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, Miscellaneous, 1933-1974 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Rönnebeck, Irmgard (A. Rönnebeck's sister), circa 1921-1947 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Rönnebeck, Irmgard (A. Rönnebeck's sister), 1921-1947 (Box 1, Folder 25-27)
  - Oversized Letter from Rönnebeck, Arnold to Louise Emerson Rönnebeck, scanned with Box 1, Folder 13, circa 1931-1936 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Writings, 1920-1944; Series 3; 6 Folders Box 1, 5
  Writings include essay drafts, notes, and poetry by the Rönnebecks, including Arnold Rönnebeck's "Paint-As-You-Go Plan," an itemized list of 31 points for artists. There is also a transcription of Matthew Arnold's poem, "Giesel's Grave."
  Materials are arranged by subject and document type.
  - Rönnebeck, Arnold, Drafts and Notes, 1941, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Rönnebeck, Arnold, Poetry, 1941, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Rönnebeck, Arnold, "Paint-As-You-Go" Plan, circa 1920-1936 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Oversized material housed in Box 5, Folder 2.
  - Rönnebeck, Arnold, "The Moon Stinks", 1942 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, Drafts and Notes, 1941-1944 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, "Geisel's Grave", 1941-1944 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Oversize "Paint-As-You-Go" Plan, scanned with Box 1, Folder 30, circa 1920-1936 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Scrapbook, 1926-1966; Series 4; 1 Folders Box 1
  The clippings scrapbook provides coverage of Louise Rönnebeck's WPA murals, commissions in Colorado and Bermuda, and various lecture and teaching appearances.
  - Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, 1926-1966 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Printed Material, 1923-1999; Series 5; 0.5 Linear feet Box 1-2
  Printed material includes articles, Christmas cards designed by Arnold Rönnebeck, clippings, exhibition announcements and catalogs of both the Rönnebecks' work, postcards collected from their travels, and other miscellaneous material.
  Portions of this series have been scanned. In some cases exhibition catalogs and other publications have had their covers, title pages, and relevant pages scanned.
  Materials are arranged by document type.
  - Articles, L. Rönnebeck's 4-G (1937), 1996, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Booklet, For Greater Service to the West (Denver National Bank Mural), 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Booklet, Saint Martin's Chapel (Reredos), 1927 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Christmas Cards, Rönnebeck, Arnold (American Artists Group), circa 1929-1936 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Christmas Cards, Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, circa 1940-1960 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Clippings, Rönnebeck, Arnold, 1923-1979 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Clippings, Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, 1926-1966 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Clippings, Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson in Colorado Episcopalian, 1952-1954 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Clippings, Miscellaneous, 1936-1972 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, Rönnebeck, Arnold, circa 1925-1942 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, circa 1940-1953 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Exhibition Catalogs, Other Artists, 1925-1945 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Periodical, Bokvännen, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Periodical, Books Abroad, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Postcards, Arizona - Grand Canyon, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Postcards, California - Avalon, La Jolla, Los Angeles and San Diego, circa 1925-1950 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Postcards, California - San Francisco, Riverside, circa 1925-1950 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Postcards, Colorado, circa 1925-1950 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Postcards, New York - Albany, Hudson River, Lake Placid, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Postcards, New York - New York City, 1923-1924 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Postcards, New York - New York City (sets), circa 1925-1950 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Postcards, Washington, D.C., 1923-1924 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Postcards, Europe and Mexico, circa 1925-1950 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, Rönnebeck, Arnold, 1925-1988 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, Rönnebeck, Louise Emerson, circa 1935-1970 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous, Colorado Springs Art Center, circa 1937-1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous, Demuth, Charles, circa 1925-1950 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous, Despiau, Matisse, Rodin, circa 1925-1970 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous, Lithography as a Fine Art, 1932, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Artwork, 1915-1950; Series 6; 2 Folders Box 2, 5
  Artwork consists of nude drawings and World War II themed sketches by Arnold Rönnebeck.
  Materials are arranged by subject.
  - Drawings, Nudes (pen and ink), circa 1915-1936 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Oversized materials housed in Box 5, Folder 3.
  - Sketches, World War II Themed, circa 1940-1950 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Oversized Drawings, Nudes, scanned with Box 2, Folder 21, circa 1915-1936 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Photographic Materials, 1884-1976; Series 7; 2.6 Linear feet Box 2-6
  Photographic materials include photos, copy prints, and negatives of the Rönnebecks and their artist friends, including Charles Demuth, Marsden Hartley, Alfred Stieglitz, and Tony Luhan. Travel photographs document vacations to Arizona, Colorado, New Mexico, New York, and Europe. Photos of Arizona and Colorado include a tour of the Grand Canyon, old mining towns, and mountain skylines. Photos from New Mexico include a trip to a Native American village and views of Tony and Mabel Luhan's residence in Taos. The photos from New York cover trips to Lake George and Lake Placid, as well as numerous photos of iconic New York City buildings, street scenes, aerial views, and the skyline from the Hudson River. Formal and informal documentation of artwork includes 7 glass plate negatives and covers the Rönnebecks' exhibitions, portfolios, and samples of public and private art commissions, including portrait busts of Ananda Coomaraswamy, Charles Lindbergh, Georgia O'Keeffe, and Carl Sandburg.
  The bulk of this series has been scanned. Negatives, duplicates, and blank versos of photographs have not been scanned.
  Materials are organized by subject. Glass plate negatives are housed separately and closed to researchers.
  - Photographs of Arnold Rönnebeck, 1907-1924 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Photographs of Arnold Rönnebeck, World War I, 1914-1917 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Photographs of Arnold Rönnebeck, with "Grief" Sculpture, circa 1930-1945 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Photographs of Arnold Rönnebeck, with Marsden Hartley Bust, circa 1925-1940 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Photographs of Louise Emerson Rönnebeck, circa 1914-1965 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Tintypes of Arnold and Louise Emerson Rönnebeck, circa 1930-1940 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Negatives of Ursula Rönnebeck and Travels, circa 1920-1955 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Photographs and Negatives of Irmgard Rönnebeck (A. Rönnebeck's sister), circa 1928 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    Oversized material housed in Box 5, Folder 4.
  - Photographs of the Emerson and Rönnebeck Families, 1884-1929 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Photographs and Negatives of Alfred Stieglitz and Georgia O'Keeffe in Lake George, New York, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Photographs and Negatives of Charles Demuth, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Includes bust sculpture.
  - Photographs of Marsden Hartley, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Photographs and Negatives of Marsden Hartley in Colorado, circa 1915-1940 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Photographs of Tony Luhan and the Rönnebecks, circa 1928 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Photograph of House, circa 1930-1960 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Photographs and Negatives, Arizona - Grand Canyon, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Photographs and Negatives, California, circa 1925-1940 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Photographs and Negatives, California - Los Angeles, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Photographs and Negatives, California - San Diego, circa 1925-1940 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Photographs and Negatives, California - San Diego and Mexico, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    Includes photographs of Mexico.
  - Photographs and Negatives, California - Santa Barbara, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Photographs and Negatives, Colorado, 1929-1930 (Box 2, Folder 44-45)
  - Photographs and Negatives, Colorado - Central City, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Photographs and Negatives, Illinois - Chicago, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Photographs, Nebraska - Omaha, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Photographs and Negatives, New Mexico, 1925-1928 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Photographs and Negatives, New Mexico - Laguna, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Photographs and Negatives, New Mexico - Santa Fe, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Photographs and Negatives, New Mexico - Taos, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Photographs and Negatives, New Mexico - Taos (Luhan residence), 1925 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - Photographs, New Mexico, Pueblo Churches and Altars, circa 1925-1945 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Photographs and Negatives, New York - New York City, 1924 (Box 3, Folder 4-8)
  - Photographs, New York - Lake George, 1924 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Photographs and Negatives, New York - Lake Placid and Hudson River, circa 1924 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Photographs and Negatives, New York - Hudson River, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Photographs and Negatives, New York and Europe, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Photographs and Negatives, Washington, D.C., circa 1925-1950 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Photographs and Negatives, Europe, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Photograph Album, Germany, Altenhof, circa 1925-1950 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Photographs, Mexico, 1925 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Denver Art Museum Exhibition, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Bas Reliefs, circa 1925-1955 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Oversized material housed with Box 5, Folder 5.
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Bas Relief, Carl Sandburg, circa 1925-1955 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Bas Reliefs, Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, circa 1925-1955 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Bas Relief, Denver National Bank, circa 1925-1955 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Photographs and Negatives of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Bas Reliefs, "La Fonda" Harvey House, circa 1925-1955; 7 Copy prints; 5 Glass negatives; 16 Photographic prints (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Bas Relief, Post Office (Longmont, Colorado), 1936 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Bas Relief and Busts, Arnold Jr. and Ursula Rönnebeck, circa 1925-1955 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Bas Relief and Busts (Omaha, NE), circa 1925-1955 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Oversized material housed in Box 5, Folder 6.
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Busts, Men, circa 1915-1955 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Oversized material housed with Box 6, Folder 1.
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Busts, Women, circa 1925-1955 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Bust, Ananda Coomaraswami, circa 1925-1955 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Bust, Georgia O'Keeffe, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Paintings Inspired by World War II, circa 1945-1955 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Pediment, Denver City Hall, circa 1925-1955 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Posters, Colorado and National Parks, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Posters, World War II Themed, circa 1940-1955 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Prints, circa 1925-1955 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Reredo, Church of the Holy Redeemer, circa 1925-1955 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Reredos, St. Martin's Chapel, circa 1925-1955 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Sculptures, circa 1915-1955 (Box 3, Folder 37-38)
    Oversized materials housed in Box 6, Folder 2.
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Sculptures, circa 1925-1955 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Sculpture, A. Rönnebeck, circa 1925-1955 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Sculpture, Blanche K. Ide Renenllow, circa 1925-1955 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Sculpture, "Eagle" (Charles Lindbergh), circa 1925-1955 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Sculpture, "Grief", circa 1925-1955 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    Oversized material housed in Box 6, Folder 2.
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Sculpture, Hodge Memorial Cemetery, 1929 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Sculpture, Homage to Maurice Ravel, circa 1925-1955 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Sculpture, "Waste", circa 1915-1940 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Photographs of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, "Paintings and Frescoes" Exhibition, circa 1930-1955 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, Frescoes, circa 1930-1955 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Photographs and Negatives of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, Frescoes in Private Homes, circa 1925-1955; 1 Copy prints; 5 Photographic prints; 2 Glass negatives (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Oversized material housed in Box 6, Folder 3.
  - Photographs of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, Murals, Bermuda, circa 1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, Murals, Competitions, circa 1925-1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Photographs of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, Murals, Temperance, circa 1925-1955 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Photographs of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, Mural, Albany Hotel (Denver), 1948 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Photographs of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, Mural, Church of the Holy Redeemer, circa 1925-1955 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Photographs of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, Mural, Cosmopolitan Hotel, circa 1925-1955 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Photographs of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, Mural, Denver Children's Hospital, circa 1925-1955 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Photographs of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, Mural, Denver City Hall, 1936, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Photographs of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, Mural, Morey Jr. High, circa 1925-1955 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Photographs of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, Mural, Post Office (Grand Junction, CO), circa 1925-1955 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Photographs of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, Mural, Post Office (Worland, WY), circa 1925-1955 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Photographs of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, Mural, Speer Memorial Hospital, circa 1925-1955 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Photographs of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, Murals, USO Service Center, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Photographs of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, Mural, Weld County Hospital, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Photographs of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, Paintings Owned by Estate, circa 1925-1955 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Photographs of Artwork by L. Rönnebeck, Paintings with Unknown Ownership, circa 1925-1955 (Box 4, Folder 19-20)
  - Oversized Photograph of Irmgard Rönnebeck, scanned with Box 2, Folder 30, circa 1928 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Oversized Photographs of Artwork by A. Rönnebeck, Bas Reliefs, scanned with Box 3, Folders 18, 20-22, circa 1925-1955 (Box 5, Folder 5)